(2003年7月4日)
帮帮忙
Help!
嘿 在这边
Hey, over here!
在这边
Over here!
她在这边
She's in there.
和我说说那个女孩吧
So tell me about the girl.
(几周前)
这...
Well...
其实如果不是因为你 我原本不可能遇见她
actually never would have met her if it weren't for you.
所以可以说这都是你的错
So in a way, this is kind of all your fault.
查理 请和我解释一下
Please enlighten me, Charlie.
如果要我完全说实话 艾尔舒医生
If I'm being a hundred percent totally honest with you here, Dr. Altschul,
这些每周的咨询并非我最爱的午后活动
these weekly sessions are not exactly my favorite afternoon activity.
(失踪人口)
但去年秋天起 我妈同意我自己开车到城里
But last fall, my mom started to let me drive into the city myself.
也就是说咨询结束后 我可以自由地闲逛
Which meant, when we were done here, I was free to wander.
(A1唱片店)
我们是高中同窗
We went to high school together.
也不算同窗 她高我一级
Well, not together. She was a year ahead of me,
已经毕业了 在纽约大学读书
already graduated and started at NYU.
我们不算是朋友 但她就是个令我难忘的人
It's not like we were friends or anything, but she's just hard to forget.
我认识你
I know you.
嗨 请问你是
Hey. How do I know you?
我们应该都上过花山高中
I think we both went to Flower Hill High.
我是说 我仍然在那里读书
Well, I mean I still do.
查尔斯威斯巴格 叫我查理就好
Charles Weisbarger. Charlie's good.
查尔斯 你怎么跑到这了
Well, Charles, what are you doing all the way out here?
我是说...大家跑到这里不都是
I mean I-- What's anyone doing out here just
想要逃离长岛 对吧
getting the hell off Long Island, right?
答案正确
That is the right answer.
所以你有什么毛病
So, what's wrong with you?
要看医生
Your doctor's appointment?
- 不是那种医生 - 是 可不是嘛
- It's not that kind of doctor. - Yeah. No shit.
你一个人来城里 绝对是来看心理医生
You're coming into the city solo. It's got to be a shrink.
你的家长要分开
Are your parents splitting up?
那是我第一次和心理健康 专业人士打交道的原因
That's when I had my first brush with a mental health professional.
我爸去年九月去世了 所以...
My dad died last September. So...
是
Yeah.
你想看我的杂志吗
Do you wanna see my zine?
什么杂志
What's a zine?
算是半个自传
It's semi-autobiographical.
(千舞之地)
是我 但又不是我
Me, but not me.
(你好 我叫怪胎)
是我的摄影 插画 音乐评论
My photography, illustrations, music reviews.
我认识这些乐队的人
These guys I know are in this band,
(前事追溯)
我想记录他们的活动 文化
and I'm trying to document their whole scene,
但他们对拍照和隐私很敏感 所以我记录得很隐晦
but they're kind of weird about photos and privacy, so it's thinly veiled.
改了名字以保护当事人
Names changed to protect the guilty.
这好棒啊
This is amazing.
我觉得我们花山的孩子应该互相支持
I think us Flower Hill kids need to stick together.
从今以后 查尔斯 你就是我的课题
From now on, Charles, you're gonna be my project.
每周我从你这里离开后 我们都会见面
We met up every week after I left here with you.
也许你可以说 我真正的教育是从那时开始的
And I guess that's when you could say my real education began.
(迈克布隆伯格 纽约领袖)
(鲁迪朱利安尼 市长)
(靴子)
来吧
Come on.
抱歉
Sorry.
你很帅气
You look good.
在她身边 你实际上是无法感到悲伤的
It was physically impossible to be sad when she was around.
真不错
Really good.
和许多其他很酷的音乐很像 但有点...
It's like a lot of other cool things, but it's kind of like--
好的 我知道 还没完呢
Okay. I know. It's not done yet.
抱歉
Sorry.
《黄铜战术》是前事追溯的唯一专辑
Brass Tactics was the only album Ex Post Facto made
在比利三棍解散乐队前
before Billy Three-Sticks broke up the band,
还没有走红就解散了
before they ever had a chance to get big.
但奇怪的是
And in a weird way,
他们只做了一张专辑这点 让这张专辑更加特别了
the fact that they only made one album makes it even more special.
- 你必须拥有一张 - 不 我没有钱
- You must own it. - No, I don't have any money.
我大概可以在LimeWire上下载吧
I mean, I could probably just download it off LimeWire, right?
不
No.
查尔斯 那会让乐队 失去他们辛苦赚的版税钱
Charles, that would deprive the band of their well-earned royalties.
- 我送你 - 不行
- I'm buying. - No.
行
Yes.
听起来 这是在纽约度过秋天的绝佳方式
That sounds like a wonderful way to spend autumn in New York.
对...是的
Yeah. Yeah, it was.
后来就不是了 虽然我猜那只能怪我
Until it wasn't. Although I guess there's no one to blame for that but me.
我的妈妈 当然了
Well, my mom, obviously.
你不是说你整夜不归家 然后在早上开车回去
Didn't you tell me you stayed out all night and then drove home in the morning,
没穿上衣 因为宿醉呕吐
shirtless and vomiting from a hangover?
好的
Okay.
我的原话不是那样 但是 对
Well-- I didn't exactly say it like that, but yeah, sure.
新年前夕总是会发生些事
I mean, New Year's Eve, shit happens.
你觉得你母亲决定
And do you think your mother's decision
对你关禁闭六个月不合理吗
to ground you for six months was unreasonable?
这和我妈无关
This isn't about my mom.
这是关于小萨 关于我爱她 以及也许她也爱我
This is about Sam and how I love her and that maybe she loves me.
我不知道 我...
And like, I don't know. I--
但我还没想清楚
But before I could even figure all that out,
就无法再见她了 所以...
I wasn't allowed to see her anymore, so--
我的故事就这样中止了
My story just stopped.
查理 这点很鼓舞人 你可以这么清楚地诉说
It's encouraging, Charlie, that you can speak so clearly
你失去的感受
about your sense of loss.
我只希望你愿意
I just wish you would talk about
也这样感性地谈论失去父亲的事
the loss of your father in the same perceptive way.
(1998年 坎托菲茨杰拉德赛)
你觉得有没有可能 通过专注于萨曼莎的事
Do you think it's possible that focusing on Samantha
你借此回避自己关于父亲的感受
is a way of deflecting your feelings about your dad?
- ...飞机的 真的  - 绝对是737
- ...from the plane. Really? - It's definitely a 737.
(永远缅怀)
有人撞上了世界贸易中心 我不知道
Somebody hit the World Trade Center. I don't know.
发生什么了
What the hell is happening?
这样对你来说更容易
It's easier to feel the way you feel
为一个住在几公里外 生机勃勃的年轻女子情绪波动
about a vibrant young woman living a few miles away
而不是去处理 失去你父亲而造成的深重 永久创伤
than it is to process the deep, permanent loss of your father.
...正爆炸 这里有人
...exploded right now. We got people all over here
在街道中央
down in the middle of the street.
又一次撞击 刚撞上另一栋楼
Another hit. It just hit another building.
两架飞机撞上了 曼哈顿下城的世界贸易中心
Two aircraft crashed into the World Trade Center in lower Manhattan.
- 等等... - 发生了爆炸...
- Wait, wait, wait. - We've got an explosion--
我的天啊 一定是个人
Oh, my God. It must be a person.
- 哪里  - 不 拜托
- Where? - No, please.
- 哪里  - 天啊
- Where? - Oh, my God.
我的天
Good Lord.
没有言语可描述
There are no words.
嘿 查理 是爸爸 出了点事
Hey, Charlie, it's Dad. Something's happened.
你大概已经在新闻上看到了
You've probably seen it on the news.
我觉得我回不了家了
I don't think I'll be coming home.
我只想要你知道我爱你
I just want you to know I love you.
相信我 医生 这一整件事 没有任何“容易”可言
Trust me, doc, there's nothing easy about it.
- 喂 - 嗨 陌生人
- Hello. - Hey, stranger.
你还在关禁闭
You still grounded?
答案最好是“没有” 因为前事追溯
The answer better be "no" because Ex Post Facto,
希望我不在的这段时间 他们仍是你最爱的乐队
who I hope in my absence is still your favorite band,
他们会在4号开重聚演唱会
is reuniting for a concert on the Fourth.
没有比利三棍不能算重聚
I mean, it's not really a reunion without Billy Three-Sticks,
他们也改了名 但是会表演所有歌曲
and they changed the name, but they're playing all their songs.
一定会很传奇
It's going to be legendary.
如果错过 你一定不会放过自己
You'd basically kill yourself if you missed it.
喂
Hello?
- 查尔斯 在吗 你听到了吗  - 是的...当然
- Hello, Charles? Are you in? - Yes. Yes, of course.
我...对 我不会错过的
I-- Yeah, I wouldn't miss it.
好的 可是
Okay, but?
可是 没有可是
But, nothing.
只是我们这么久没聊过
It's just we haven't really talked in so long.
我知道 我试过打给你 但你没回电话
I know. I tried calling you, but you never called back.
是 抱歉 我只是觉得我没什么可说的
Yeah, sorry, I just didn't feel like I had anything to say.
是 如果我和你的禁足有任何关系 那我深表抱歉
No, I'm sorry for any role that I may have played in your incarceration.
不是 对
No. Yeah.
你知道吗 那段日子真的是...
You know what? That was a time of real...
成长和内省的机会 所以...
real growth and introspection, so...
我开玩笑的 烂透了 我很想你
I'm kidding. It sucked. I missed you.
这话让我好难过
That makes me sad.
但也让我很高兴
But it also makes me very happy
因为我想死你了 查尔斯
because I've missed the hell out of you, Charles.
好了 我得挂了 但7月4号活动详情稍后再说
Okay, I got to go, but details about the Fourth of July shenanigans are to follow.
- 拜拜 - 尼基 快点
- Bye. - Nicky, hurry up!
- 小萨 走啦 - 走...
- Sammy. Let's go. - Go, go, go.
要命 你们放火烧教堂了
Holy shit! You guys torched a fucking church?
你觉得我们做了什么 为罪孽忏悔吗
What'd you think we were doing? Confessing our sins?
快上车 走啦
Get in the car. Come on!
- 女士们 快点 磨蹭什么呢  - 你们做了什...
- Ladies. Come on. What are we doing? - Why did you do--
为什么以教堂为目标
Why did you target a fucking church?
- 尼基去哪了  - 不知道
- Where's Nicky? Where's Nicky? - I don't know.
- 等等 不能落下尼基 - 他来了
- Wait, we can't leave without Nicky. - He's coming.
- 尼基 - 你们做了什么事
- Nicky! - What the fuck did you guys do?
- 走 快点啊 - 快点 我们走
- Go. Come on! - Come on. Let's move!
- 我们不能抛下你 - 快点
- We can't leave without you. - Hurry it up!
真美啊 对吧
She's a thing of beauty, isn't she?
快走
Let's go!
我们得离开这里
We need to get the fuck outta here.
走 踩油门
Go! Step on it.
快 小萨
Come on, Sam.
噢 美丽广阔的苍穹
O beautiful for spacious skies
金黄的稻浪
For amber waves of grain
壮丽的紫山
For purple mountain majesties
硕果累累的平原之上
Above the fruited plain
美国...
America--
妮什玛古普帕
Nishima Guptpa.
凯特汉密尔顿斯维尼兰普莱特
Cate Hamilton-Sweeney Lamplighter.
- 保重 - 非常感谢
- Take care. - Thank you so much.
是 对 拜拜
Yes. Yep. Bye-bye.
凯特汉密尔顿斯维尼兰普莱特 她的母亲
Cate Hamilton-Sweeney Lamplighter, her mother.
- 能指给我看是哪位吗  - 为什么
- Can you point her out for me? - Why?
我觉得我可能认识她的兄弟
I think I might know her brother.
- 你认识汉密尔顿斯维尼家的人  - 对
- You know a Hamilton-Sweeney? - Yeah.
有人脉 那边
Impressive. Over there.
那太好了 她会很高兴
That'll be great. She'll love that.
但下次换你家 真的
But it's your place next time, like, truly.
- 不好意思 打扰一下 - 嗨
- Excuse me. Sorry. - Hi.
我想介绍一下自己 墨瑟古德曼
I just wanted to introduce myself. Mercer Goodman.
幸会 我是...你...
Nice to meet you. I'm-- Are--
- 你是凯特的老师吗  - 不
- Are you one of Cate's teachers? - No.
我有个朋友 是...
I'm a friend of--
我觉得他可能是你兄弟 威廉
I think he might be your brother. William.
蕾根 快点 孩子们在等
Regan, come on. Kids are waiting.
- 我答应他们让他们吃意大利雪糕 - 是
- I may have promised them gelato. - Yeah.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
是这样 现在不太方便聊 但是很高兴...
Look, now is not a great time, but it was really nice--
很高兴认识你 古德曼先生
It was really great to meet you, Mr. Goodman.
她终于睡着了 她好激动
She's asleep, finally. She was so excited.
做得好
Well done.
你没事吧 你看起来有点心不在焉
Everything okay with you? You seem a little distracted.
我没事 只是我担心威尔
I'm fine. It's just I'm worried about Will.
你知道 他最近不在状态
You know, he's just not himself these days.
他以前很喜欢放假前最后一天 而我就是不懂
He used to love the last day of school, and I just, I don't get it.
对 他以前喜欢过很多东西
Yeah. He used to love a lot of things.
棒球卡
Baseball cards.
宠物小精灵
Pokémon.
宠物小精灵 他的父母
Pokémon. His parents.
不过是个阶段 他是个好孩子
It's just a phase. He's a good kid.
(蕾根)
(他在对你洒谎)
我们要不要聊聊你背着我出轨的事情
Are we gonna talk about how you've been cheating on me?
什么 出轨
What? Cheating?
吉斯 你靠撒谎 洗脱自己罪名的机会已经没了
Keith, the window where you could bullshit your way out of this has closed.
她给我写了张字条
She wrote me a note.
虽然我本来就有所怀疑
Not that I didn't already suspect though.
你什么时候开始听 放荡乐团的歌 她是25岁吗
Since when do you listen to The Libertines? What is she, 25?
等等
Hold on.
如果你想聊 那我们就聊 但别说得好像这都是我的错
If you want to talk, let's talk. But don't act like this is all my fault.
天啊 真抱歉
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
我忘记提我背着你出轨那部分了 我都不知道我有个男友
I missed the part where I cheated on you. I had no idea that I had a boyfriend.
对 有时感觉你也没有丈夫
Yeah, well, sometimes it feels like you don't have a husband either.
她觉得你令人着迷吗
Does she find you fascinating?
她是不是个自由的灵魂 特别有灵动的气质
Is she so free-spirited and totally fucking alive?
对 算是吧
Yeah, kind of.
她有工作吗
Does she have a job?
她有两个孩子吗 生病的父亲
Does she have two kids? A sick father?
天啊 吉斯 我曾是那个女孩 我...
God, Keith, I was that girl. I--
我曾是那个女孩 我掐死了她 好让我们拥有现在的生活
I was that girl, and I strangled her so that we could have this.
该死
Fuck.
古德曼先生
Mr. Goodman.
嗨 很高兴赶上你在
Hi, I'm glad I caught you.
我刚打算给孩子的老师送份礼物
I was just dropping off a gift to my kid's teacher,
我想我们可以继续 之前的谈话或是重新开始
and I thought we could finish our conversation or start it.
你认识我弟弟
You know my brother?
对 威廉是我的朋友 是一位好友
Yes, William is a friend. A good friend.
不过可能也没那么好 毕竟在那天之前
Although maybe not that good, since until the other day,
我都不知道他有姐妹
I didn't know he had a sister.
我们好多年没见了
Well, we haven't seen each other in years,
所以我不知道 他是不是还住在城里 还是死了
so I didn't know if he was living in the city still or dead.
所以我松了一口气
So, I'm relieved.
你想换个地方聊吗
Would you like to go somewhere we can talk?
我真的很想 但是我得走了
I would love that more than you know. But I have to go.
我得去家里见搬运工
I'm meeting movers at the house.
搬家是最烦心的
Moving, that's always the worst.
对 尤其是未经计划的
Yeah, especially when it's unplanned.
希望一切顺利
Well, everything's okay I hope?
是 一切都不顺
Yeah, everything is shit.
但是 多谢关心 你很善良
But thanks for asking. You're very sweet.
听着 如果你在4号前见到他
Well, listen, if you see him, before the Fourth,
能给他这个吗
would you give him this?
是 告诉他我很想他...
Yeah. Just tell him I miss him and that...
发生了很多变化
a lot has changed.
对 告诉他我今年真的需要他陪伴
Yeah, just tell him I really need him there this year.
没问题
Of course.
很欢迎你来 墨瑟
And I would love for you to come, Mercer.
见到你很开心
It was a pleasure meeting you.
我很高兴威廉身边有人
I'm glad William's got someone.
(威廉哈密尔顿斯维尼)
生日快乐...
Happy birthday, happy birthday.
天啊 这些插画
Oh, my gosh. These illustrations.
真美
Beautiful.
这...是我们
And this-- This is us.
这是我们的恋爱时期
Well, this is our courtship.
如果可以用这个词
If you can call it that.
在布鲁诺的小屋的那个周末 这是我的艺术汇演
The weekend at Bruno's cabin. This is my art show.
这是我们在屋顶上坐着谈天的 那些夜晚 然后...
This is just all those nights we sat up on the roof, just talking, and...
来 和自恋狂艺术家同居 总要有些好处的 对吧
Come on. Gotta be some upside to living with a narcissistic artist, right?
是
Yeah.
对 来 打开 里面有真的礼物
All right. Let's go. Open it. There's a real present inside.
威廉 我的天啊
William. Oh, my gosh.
谢谢你
Thank you.
真的 你没有必要送我这么奢侈的东西
Truly, you really did not have to get me something so extravagant.
这个嘛
Well,
作为一项对你未来的投资
as an investment in your future,
它算是挺便宜的
it came pretty cheap.
我出门了
I'm going out.
在我生日时
On my birthday?
我只是去一趟工作室 好吗
I'm just gonna go to the studio for a little bit. All right?
我会在晚餐前回家 我保证
I will be home before dinner. I promise.
没事啦 你可以安装你的新电脑 可以开始写你的新小说了
Come on, you can set up your new computer and you can start that new novel of yours.
别这样看我
Don't look at me like that.
我没有怎样看你
I'm not looking at you in any particular way.
只是这是我离开家后的第一个生日
It's just it is my first birthday away from home.
对 你已经提过几次了
Right, as you've mentioned a couple times now,
而...
and...
如果今天没达到你的预期 那我很抱歉
I'm sorry if today is falling short of whatever you had in your head,
但是你不觉得你仍把乔治亚 称为家这一点很暴露你的想法吗
but does it strike you as revealing that you still refer to Georgia as home?
家 也就是我的家乡 至少我仍然会聊
Home, as in where I came from. At least I still talk about it.
是
Right.
因为你是一个开诚布公的人
'Cause you are just a man of transparency and honesty.
你是怎么向你父母描述我的
How do you describe me to your parents?
什么 你的室友
What is it? Your roommate?
听着 你不懂 这没那么简单
Look, you don't understand. It's not that easy.
对他们还是对你
For them or for you?
请告诉我这和
Please just tell me this has nothing to do with that
- 你一有机会就拱到我面前的... - 好吧
- fucking envelope that you keep shoving... - All right.
- ...那封信无关 - 威尔 你打算打开它吗
- ...into my field of vision. - Will, are you ever going to open it?
是你家人写的
It is from your family.
我想知道的是它是怎么进入我们公寓的
What I want to know is how it got into our apartment.
我想知道的是为什么你不和他们说话
What I want to know is why you don't talk to them.
- 他们那么... - 有钱
- They're so-- - Rich?
我是想说友善 至少你姐姐是
I was gonna say nice. At least your sister is.
好的
Okay.
我出门了
I'm going out.
我们是成年人了 墨瑟
We're grown men, Merce.
过生日对我们的年龄来说有点幼稚
Birthdays are a little ridiculous at our age.
(贝尔与塞巴斯蒂安 《阿拉伯皮带男孩》)
快点 你在里面太久了
Hurry up. You've been in there way too long.
- 他在里面太久了 - 你担心过多 没事的
- He's been in there way too long. - You worry too much. It's all good.
没事的
It's all good.
等等 你都装满了  你说我爸不会注意到的
Wait. You filled up that whole thing? You said my dad wouldn't notice.
他不会的 而且你说了 他现在都不怎么工作了
He won't. Plus, you said he doesn't even work much anymore.
- 他也不需要 - 该死的 索尔
- It's not like he needs it. - Fuck, Sol.
这是没有受害者的罪行 我从没来过这里
It's a victimless crime. I was never here.
我们从没来过这里
We were never here.
一起吗
Coming with?
我还有事 今晚见吧
I got some shit to do. I'll see you tonight.
(宇宙龙烟火)
希望我们没闯大祸 你拿了好多
I hope we didn't just fuck up. You took a lot.
他爸是个废物酒鬼
Her dad's a washed-up drunk.
对 但他和小萨很亲近 她知道那东西有多危险
Yeah, but he and Sam are close. And she knows how dangerous that shit is.
(美妙烟火)
嘿 我正希望你打来 也许你准备好聊了
Hey, I was hoping you'd call. You might be ready to talk.
为什么 因为你有些 关于自己行为的全新 深刻见解
Why? Because you have some new and profound
你想要分享
insights you'd like to share on your behavior?
更准确的是我想你的声音了
More like I missed your voice.
少来
Stop.
这几周很疯狂
It's been a crazy couple of weeks.
我只是打来问你 今晚什么时候回来我爸家
I'm just calling to see what time you're coming to my dad's tonight.
- 我以为你不希望我去 - 我不希望
- I didn't think you wanted me to go. - I don't.
但我们每年都去 今年也邀请了你
But we go every year and you were invited.
糟糕 小蕾 你还没告诉他
Oh, shit, Reggie. You haven't told him yet.
对 因为这事应该当面说
No, because it should be in person.
而且爸在明尼阿波利斯的诊所 我不想打扰他
And Dad's in Minneapolis at the clinic. I didn't want to bother him.
还是你仍希望我们能和好
Or you're still hoping we can work it out?
你这是在异想天开 真的想太多
You're delusional, like, truly delusional.
也许我是乐观主义者
Maybe I'm an optimist?
也许你是希望我会原谅你
Or maybe you're hoping that I'll forgive you
这样你就不用继续当坏人了
so that you don't have to be the bad guy anymore.
我搞砸了 不意味着以后都如此
I fucked up. Doesn't mean it has to be forever.
你搞砸了
You fucked up?
搞砸说的是钥匙锁在车里
Fucking up is locking your keys in the car.
搞砸说的是把电影票落在家里
Fucking up is leaving your theater tickets at home.
你做的“好事”根本不能用这个词形容
It does not begin to describe what you did.
你对我们做的事
What you've done to us.
吉斯 如果你曾看过心理医生 或是读过自助书籍
Keith, if you'd ever been to therapy, or read a self-help book,
或上网搜过“我为什么是大混蛋”
or googled, "Why am I such a fucking asshole,"
也许你就会明白 为什么我们不可能和好如初
then maybe you'd understand why there's no fixing this.
我做了件糟糕的事 但我爱你 我爱我们的孩子
I did a terrible thing, but I love you. I love our kids.
如果你希望我去看心理医生 我会去的
If you want me to go to therapy, I'll go to therapy.
吉斯 今晚我会告诉父亲我要离婚
Keith, tonight I'm going to tell my father that I'm ending my marriage.
欢迎你加入这次谈话
You are welcome to be a part of that conversation.
我不打算捂住你的嘴
I'm not trying to bury you.
小蕾 他知道 你会和我离婚只可能是因为我出轨
Reggie, he knows the only reason you'd end our marriage is if I cheated on you.
我们离婚是因为你 而他怎么想是我不能控制的
You ended our marriage and I can't control what he thinks.
这次对话毫无意义
This conversation was pointless.
- 你到底会不会去  - 是 我会去的
- Are you gonna be there or not? - Yeah. I'll be there.
晚点见
I'll see you later.
各位乘客 请注意
Attention, passengers.
我不相信 传说中的比利三棍
I don't believe it. Billy fucking Three-Sticks.
索罗门格朗吉
Solomon Grungy.
世界上那么多车站 偏偏啊
Of all the terminals in the world, huh?
你的袋子里装着什么 是尸体吗
What you got in that bag? Is there a body in there?
是我认识的人吗
Anyone I know?
是曲棍球训练 只有皇后区有免费冰场
It's hockey practice. Only free ice is in Queens.
你好吗 尼基怎么样
How you doing? How's Nicky?
为什么每次有人遇见我 总是要问尼基怎么样
Why is it that every time someone sees me, they ask how Nicky's doing?
寒暄而已 只是表示礼貌
As a pleasantry. That's all. Half-assed, by the way.
拜托 我只是想知道 乐队解散后你们过得怎么样
Come on. I just want to know how y'all are surviving without the band.
尼基没联系你
Nicky hasn't reached out?
没有 他为什么会
No. Why would he?
我们今晚在唐希尔有演出
We booked a gig at Don Hill's tonight.
乐队重聚
Getting the band back together.
名为“从无到有”
Calling it Ex Nihilo.
还有海报 天
With a flyer? Wow.
这是个烂主意 名字更烂
That is a shitty idea, with an even shittier name.
把你的名字也加进去
Put you on the list?
7月4日 索尔 我有计划了
Fourth of July, Sol. I got plans.
- 嗨 - 重要计划
- Hi. - Big plans.
- 是吗  - 是
- Yeah? - Yeah.
去地铁站拉客
Cruising the train station?
今晚去吧 也许你会有惊喜
Show up tonight. You might be surprised.
那是比利三棍 你应该介绍我的
That was Billy Three-Sticks. You could've introduced me.
不
No.
为什么
Why not?
你答应过不再打给我的
You agreed you wouldn't call me anymore.
我们得谈谈
We need to talk.
别担心 我不是怀孕了
Don't worry, I'm not pregnant or anything.
但事关重要 不过必须当面谈
But it's important, and it has to be in person.
现在不太方便
Now's not a good time.
好的 那么今晚
Okay. Well, then, later tonight?
今晚我得去我岳父家参加一个派对
Tonight I have to go to a party at my father-in-law's,
他到时候一定会得知
where he'll undoubtedly discover
我背着他的女儿和一个大学生出轨
that I cheated on his daughter with a college student.
好的 在派对前见我吧
Okay. Meet me before the party.
晚上9点在唐希尔 春街和格林尼治街 是个夜店
Don Hill's at 9:00 p.m. Spring and Greenwich. It's a club.
不 我们没什么可聊的
No, we have nothing to talk about.
好吧 如果你不来见我 那我只能去找你了
Okay. If you don't come to me, then I'm gonna have to come to you.
萨曼莎 别这么做
Samantha, don't do that.
那次去大都会时 你指给我看是哪栋楼
You showed me where the building was that time we went to the Met.
请别这么做 求求你 请远离我和我的家人
Please don't do that. Please. Please, stay away from me and my family.
我已经说了 给你老婆字条的不是我
I already told you, I'm not the one who sent that note to your wife.
但我觉得我知道是谁给的
But I think that I might know who did.
有些人不希望我们在一起
There are people who don't want us to be together and
我之前没告诉你 因为我不懂
I didn't tell you before because I didn't understand.
但现在我开始懂了
But now I'm starting to,
我真的很担心会发生不好的事
and I'm really worried that something bad is gonna happen.
对 不好的事已经发生了
Yeah, something bad has already happened.
有什么比毁了我的婚姻更糟的
What can be worse than blowing up my marriage?
毁了其他的东西
Blowing up something else.
(易燃 远离火源)
- 喂  - 嘿 是我
- Hello? - Hey, it's me.
出了点事
So, something has come up.
我今晚得去看一个乐队的演出
And I kind of need to see this band tonight.
其实是我的乐队 只不过少了我和其他重要的成员
It's my band actually, minus me and anyone else that fucking matters.
我以为我们要去巴特利公园看烟火
I thought we were going to Battery Park to watch the fireworks.
嘿 和我一起去吧...拜托
Hey, come with me. Come with me. Come on, please.
宝贝 我必须得去看他们演出
Babe? I can't not be there for this.
我得亲眼看看这场闹剧
I have to see this fucking travesty unfold with my own two eyes.
你知道 我感觉不太舒服
You know, I'm feeling just a little under the weather.
浑身疼 像流感 你读过关于SARS的事吗
Achy, fluey. Have you read about SARS?
- 我不想传染别人 - 我的天啊
- I wouldn't wanna infect anyone. - Oh, my God.
你没有得SARS 墨瑟
You do not have SARS, Merce.
好吧 行 你就留在家里
Okay, fine. Just stay home,
照顾好自己 多喝水
be good to yourself and drink lots of fluids.
我们回头见 好吗
And I'll see you later. Okay?
- 拜拜 - 拜拜
- Bye. - Bye.
(威廉哈密尔顿斯维尼先生及夫人)
(邀请您参加鸡尾酒会 庆祝7月4号国庆日)
小萨
Sam!
嗨
Hi.
今晚准备好了
Are you ready for tonight?
是的 我什么都准备好了 一切
Yes. I'm ready for anything. Everything.
你带票了吗 还是...
So do you have the tickets, or--
什么票 地铁票
Tickets for what? For the train?
前事追溯的票
For Ex Post Facto.
又不是歌剧表演 小白 没有门票
It's not the opera, rookie. There are no tickets.
而且现在他们叫从无到有
Also, it's Ex Nihilo now.
天 没了我 你做了什么
God, what did you do without me?
等等 抱歉 你能等下吗
Wait, sorry. Can you hold on?
- 你能等下吗 我得... - 快点 地铁20分钟后出发
- Can you wait? I need to-- - Hurry up. Our train's in 20 minutes.
- 地铁20分钟后出发 - 抱歉 我马上来
- Our train's in 20 minutes. - Sorry, I'm coming.
嘿 威尔
Hey, Will?
威尔
Will?
- 怎么了  - 桑托斯太太在路上了
- What? - Mrs. Santos is on her way.
法律上 是由她负责 但你能不能帮忙看下妹妹
Legally, she's in charge, but can you just keep an eye on your sister, please?
大家 快看那鸟
Guys, look at the bird.
天啊 凯特 好漂亮
Wow, Cate. That is beautiful.
爸爸会去派对吗
Is Dad gonna be at the party?
是的 计划如此
Yeah, that's the plan.
别和他复合
Don't get back together with him.
威尔 你知道你爸很爱你
Will, you know that your dad loves you so much.
而且 这一切与你们无关
And none of this has anything to do with you.
你说是就是吧 帮我向外公问好
No shit. Say hi to Grandpa for me.
不...
N--
嘿 你的相机在哪
Hey, so, where's your camera?
你肯定想为你的杂志 记录乐队复合的时刻吧
I mean, surely you're gonna wanna document the band's reunion for your zine, right?
相机不见了
Camera's missing.
糟糕 怎么回事
Oh, shit. What happened to it?
如果我知道 就不叫“不见了” 对吧
If I knew that, it wouldn't be missing, would it?
对 不过 是你弄丢了还是被人拿走了...
Right. But, you lost it, or someone took it, or--
天啊 查尔斯 我说了 不知道
Jesus Christ, Charles. I said I don't know.
下一站是运河街
The next stop is Canal Street.
小萨 你还好吗
Sam? Are you okay?
你知道 你是唯一这么问过我的人
You know, you're the only one who ever asks me that.
(唐希尔)
- 我没有身份证 - 你不需要 你和我一起的
- I don't have ID. - You don't need an ID. You're with me.
- 嗨 - 我就知道今晚会见到你 小萨
- Hi. - I knew we'd be seeing you tonight, Sammy.
- 这瘦竹竿是谁  - 这是查尔斯 我的学徒
- Who's the beanpole? - This is Charles, my protégé.
- 嗨 - 别品头论足 他还在进步中
- Hi. - Don't judge. He's a work in progress.
你的朋友就是我的朋友
Your friends are my friends.
我就希望你这么说
I was hoping you'd say that.
查尔斯 你自己一个人待一小时没事吧
Charles, do you think you would be okay on your own for an hour?
- 我得去上城区 - 小萨 搞什么
- I have to go uptown. - What the fuck, Sam?
我以为你想今晚和我一起过
I thought you wanted to spend tonight with me.
我想 我真的想
I do. I really do.
只是...我得解决一个问题 非常紧急
I just-- There's a problem that I have to deal with, and it can't really wait.
如果我一小时后没回来 就来找我
If I'm not back in an hour, come find me.
在公园旁 第五大道和73街路口
By the park, 5th and 73rd.
拜拜
Bye.
谢谢
Thanks.
蕾根 你真美
Regan, you look wonderful.
- 这派对好奢华 恭喜你 菲莉希亚 - 谢谢
- Fabulous party. Congratulations, Felicia. - Thank you.
爸爸在哪 我想听他说说他的诊断结果
Where's Daddy? I want to hear how everything went at the clinic.
健康方面是好消息 他所有测试都通过了
Healthwise, the news is good. He passed all his tests.
所以不是失智症
So it's not dementia?
他目前的状况下什么都不需要改变
He's holding at a level where nothing needs to change.
他很高兴这不会影响工作
He's very pleased this won't affect work.
- 请为他感到高兴 - 我会的 他在哪里
- Please be happy for him. - I will. Where is he?
不巧 明尼阿波利斯有雷电风暴
Unfortunately, there was a lightning storm in Minneapolis,
G4不能飞 所以...
and the G4 is grounded, so--
你那帅哥老公呢
Where's your handsome husband?
他在路上 应该很快就到
He's coming. Soon, I think.
我应该告诉你 我们要分开...我们已经分开了
I should probably tell you that we're separating-- That we have separated.
不知道这是不是 你的艾莫里叔叔找你的原因
I'm wondering if this is why your Uncle Amory is looking for you.
我不知道艾莫里怎么会得知消息
Well, I don't know how Amory would know.
我们没告诉任何人
We haven't told anyone.
你懂的 艾莫里总有办法得知一切
You know, Amory has a way of finding out everything.
- 见到你真好 - 是 好吧
- Fabulous to see you. - Yeah. Okay.
找艾莫里叔叔吧 他很坚持 今晚一定要和你聊
Do find Uncle Amory. He's adamant about speaking with you tonight.
我会的
Yeah, I will.
我觉得你站在别人的外套上了
I think you're standing on someone's jacket.
不 那是我的
No. That's mine.
是 我一直在观察你
Yeah. I've been watching you.
我喜欢你的舞姿 什么都不在乎的样子
I like how you dance, like you don't give a shit.
谢谢
Thank you.
那么 你有携带吗
So, are you holding?
因为无论你嗑了什么 我都想要
'Cause whatever you're on, I definitely want some.
抱歉 刚嗑完
Sorry. Fresh out.
可惜 原本一定不会浪费你的货
Bummer. Would have made it worth your while.
嘿 演出结束后 我可以带你去后台
Hey, I could probably get you backstage after the show.
我是和乐队一起的
I'm with the band.
是吗
Yeah?
来吧
Come on.
好
Yeah!
黄铜战术 总有代价
Brass tactics This shit's never free
人人都在 各取所需
Everybody's inside Taking what they need
受诅咒的天主教徒 把那募捐桶给我
Curse Catholics Now pass me that collection basket
现金小费给我 来者不拒
I'd take the cash tip Any day of the week
噢
Ooh
黄铜战术
Brass tactics
大众去死
Fuck the masses
好的 老板 到了
All right, boss. We're here.
是 不...就继续开
Yeah, no-- Just keep going.
继续开 别停就好
Keep going. Just keep going.
好的
All right.
- 不 我不是... - 谢谢
- Oh, no, I'm not-- I'm, I wasn't-- - Thank you.
不好意思 我以为你在等
Apologies. I thought you were waiting.
我是在等 不过不是等车
I'm waiting, just not for the bus.
我也不确定自己在等什么
Not exactly sure what I'm waiting for.
等某个迹象 我总是在等那个
A sign, maybe? That's what I'm always waiting for.
不如让我当你的迹象 你可以当我的
How about I be yours? You can be mine.
让我们安心认定 这就是我们此刻该身处的地方
Let's just be reassured that we are exactly where we are supposed to be.
好的
Okay.
我喜欢
I like that.
我要坐在这个长凳上 不挪屁股
Then I am going to keep my butt firmly rooted to this bench.
我要走到街道那边 进入未知世界
I will cross the street into an unknown world.
人生只有一次 对吧
You only live once, right?
一次就够了 只要没有白活
Once is enough, if you do it right.
这里是国内最古老战舰的甲板
From the deck of the country's oldest battleship,
老铁壳
Old Ironsides,
前往神奇王国
to the Magic Kingdom,
来自上百个国家的数千移民
thousands of immigrants from more than a hundred nations
成为美国公民
became American citizens.
达拉斯有更多庆祝活动
And more celebrations in Dallas,
独立日这天 100位士兵归家
where Independence Day brought 100 soldiers home
他们从伊拉克和阿富汗归来 休假两周
from Iraq and Afghanistan for two weeks of R & R.
墨瑟
Mercer.
等等 你说服他来了
Wait. You got him to come?
他在哪 威廉在哪里
Where is he? Where is William?
很遗憾 他没到 不过他的衣服到了
I'm sorry to say he did not make it. Although his suit did.
白色亚麻 你穿着挺好看
White linen. You wear it well.
你在这里做什么
Well, what are you doing in here?
显然 就连威廉的精品西装
Apparently, even William's fine tailoring
也无法阻止其他宾客把我当作服务员
can't keep the other guests from mistaking me for a waiter.
三次
Three times.
你为什么藏在这里
Why are you hiding in here?
因为我喝醉了 而现在没酒
Because I'm drunk and currently drinkless.
蕾根 不 你应该让我帮你
Oh, Regan-- No, you should let me help you there.
不 没关系 我来就好 没事的...我很快的
No, it's okay. I got it. It's fine. Just fine. I'll be a second.
好吧 蕾根 请...我来就...好的
Okay. Regan, please. Just let me-- Okay.
好的 请让我帮忙 让我...
Okay. Let me help please. Let me--
- 真蠢啊 - 好了 来冲冲
- That was so stupid. - Here we go. Just put that under there.
前童子军再次现身 其实是鹰级童军
Former Boy Scout coming out. Well, Eagle Scout, actually.
- 抱歉 - 是 好的
- Sorry. - Yes. Okay.
没事
Got you here.
不会太疼吧
Doesn't hurt too bad, does it?
不 没关系
No. It's okay.
但我有止痛的
But I do have something for the pain.
在这里
In here?
不 当然不是
No, of course not.
我们必须出去抽
We got to go outside.
我和我的爱站在角落里
I was standing on the corner With my love
我没有理由忍下去
And I ain't got no reason To hold on in me
非常偶然
Real, real, real casual
离开这里
Away from here
我没有理由起来
And I ain't got no reason to get up
然后
And get
站起身
Get up off my knees
To get up off my knees
这个城市着火了 如同某人自杀了
This city's on fire Like someone committing suicide
- 来吧 - 等等
- Come on. - Wait.
- 我应该去见个人 - 走吧
- I think I'm supposed to meet someone. - Come on.
他和我一起的 可以吧
He's with me. Cool?
是 可以 没问题
Yeah, cool. No problem.
谢谢
Thank you.
我的妈 尼基
Holy shit, Nicky.
真够紧张的
That was intense.
你们刚才真出色 比利希望自己有那么出色
You guys were so good. Billy wishes he was ever that good.
- 你没看过比利的现场 - 随便啦
- You never saw Billy live. - Whatever.
这夸奖我收下了
I'll take the praise.
小子 你要加入吗 还是旁观
Are you gonna join us, kid, or you just gonna watch?
- 别说了 - 你想我怎么做
- Stop. - Which do you want me to do?
我爱这家伙
I love this dude.
- 你过来 - 来吧
- Come here. You. - Come on.
- 是 - 是 好...
- Yeah. - Yeah, oka--
给这瘦小子拿瓶啤酒
Someone get his skinny ass a beer.
你是怎么认识这位年轻人的
So, how do you know our young friend here?
我们刚认识
We just met.
下水道女孩总交新朋友
Sewer Girl's always making new friends.
小心她的男友
Just watch out for her boyfriend.
他有股狠劲 而且下巴装了金属板
He's got a mean streak and a metal plate in his jaw.
- 什...谢谢 - 给
- Wha-- Thank you. - Here.
你的下巴怎么了
What happened to your jaw?
尼基
Nicky?
- 他不是我的男友 - 什么
- He's not my boyfriend. - What?
我是
I am.
这瘦小子是谁 他把啤酒都喝光了
Who the fuck's the skinny kid drinking all the beer?
这是...
This is--
查理 嗨
Charlie. Hi.
- 这是查理 嗨 嗯  - 查理
- This is Charlie. Hi. Hmm? - Charlie.
我见过你 查理 新年前夕 你是小萨的朋友
I've seen you before, Charlie. New Year's Eve. You're Sam's friend.
对 那天晚上有点记不清了 但是 没错 有可能
Yeah. That night was kind of a blur, but yeah. It could be.
- 等等 你没说你认识小萨 - 我...你没问
- Wait. You didn't say you knew Sam. - Well, I-- You didn't ask.
我是说...但是 没错 我们可以算是最好的朋友了
I mean-- But yeah, we're, like, basically best friends.
小萨不在这里
So Sam's not here?
- 她不可能错过今晚 - 不
- There's no way she'd miss this. - No.
她不想的 我们是一起来的
She didn't want to. I mean, we came here together and stuff,
但她说她得去上城区办点事
but she said she had to do something uptown.
你们知道怎么去 第五大道和73街的路口最快吗
Do you guys know the fastest way to get to 5th and 73rd?
我应该去那里见她
I'm supposed to meet her there.
偷辆车开过去
Steal a car and drive.
嘿 SG 他们在演奏我们的歌
Hey, SG, they're playing our song.
- 来吧 - 是
- Come on. - Yeah.
拜拜 尼基
Bye, Nicky.
你们今晚的演出太精彩了
You had a great show tonight.
我不想把气氛弄怪
I don't want to be, like, weird about it. I don't wanna be weird about it.
- 是 我走了 我... - 你哪都不许去
- Yeah, I'll go. I-- - You're not going anywhere.
来吧 查理兄弟 跟我来
Come on, Charlie Man. Come with me.
- 真的  - 对 先生 你先
- Really? - Yeah. After you, sir.
去哪里
To where?
- 跟我来就好 有我在 别担心 - 好的
- Just follow me. I got you. Yeah? - Okay, yeah.
查理 你以前吸过可卡因吗
You ever done coke before, Charlie?
吸过 一次 对
Yeah. One time. Yeah.
来吧
Have at it.
是
Yeah.
像这样 疤面人
Like this, Scarface.
尼克拉斯...
Nicholas. Nicholas.
比利三棍 我的妈
Billy Three-Sticks. Holy shit.
我知道你不会甘心旁观
I knew you couldn't stay away.
我只是要确定你们不会坏了我的好名声
Just had to make sure you weren't ruining my good name.
我们有自己的名字
We have our own name.
从无到有 意思是“从虚无中诞生” 和上帝创造生命一样
Ex Nihilo. Means "out of nothing," like the way God fashioned life.
我的老天
Jesus fucking Christ.
我真高兴自己不需要
I am so glad that I don't have to listen
再听你自命不凡的胡说八道了
to your pretentious fucking bullshit anymore.
过来
Come here.
你知道 刚才还不错
You know, that wasn't half bad out there.
其实我挺喜欢的
I actually kinda liked it.
真的 我喜欢
I did. I liked it.
真抱歉
I'm so sorry.
乐队的两个人这样相见...
The two of you guys meeting up like this--
我读过小萨的杂志 关于这支乐队的历史
I've read Sam's zine about the history of this band and,
这简直是...历史时刻
I mean, this just-- this is totally epic.
我告诉她时她一定激动死了
She's going to shit herself when I tell her.
天啊 我该去找她了
Oh, God. I should go meet up with her.
她大概在等我
She's probably waiting for me.
那家伙是谁啊
Who the fuck was that guy? Huh?
多谢你过来 比利 这意义重大
Thanks for coming down, Billy. It means a lot.
你和威廉算什么
So, what's the deal with you and William?
- “算什么”  - 拜托
- "Deal"? - Oh, come on.
他是我的弟弟 你们同居吗 是认真交往
He's my brother. Do you live together? Is it serious?
对我来说是的 对威廉来说是吗
It is to me. Is it to William?
那我就不知道了
That I do not know.
他很多事都藏在心里 他的过去 家人 感受
He keeps so much to himself. His past, his family, his feelings.
他说话不经大脑
He's careless with words.
我们认识的第一晚就说他爱我
Told me he loved me on the first night we met,
虽然他知道那不是认真的
when he knew it wouldn't mean anything.
这真是典型威廉做派
Well, that's classic William.
现在你不能说他从没说过这句话了
Now you can't say he never said it.
但我永远都不会知道他说那话的真正意思
But I can never know what he means by it.
你今晚为什么来这里
So why'd you come here tonight?
因为我知道这会惹火他
Because I knew it would piss him off.
你为什么邀请我
Why'd you invite me?
同样的理由
Same, you know?
敬我们
Here's to us.
有人吗
Hello?
嗨
Hi.
蕾根汉密尔顿斯维尼兰普莱特
Regan Hamilton-Sweeney Lamplighter,
你是个牛人
you are a badass.
请把兰普莱特去掉 我已经不再用了
Please drop the "Lamplighter." I have.
别评判我 我几乎不碰这东西
And don't judge me. I hardly ever touch this stuff.
当然
Of course.
那一定是烟花
That must be the fireworks,
也就是说菲莉希亚的表演很快就开始了
which means Felicia's show is starting soon.
不 这绝对是枪声
No. Those were definitely gunshots.
不 这是上东区
No, it's the Upper East Side.
我来自南部 我们懂枪
I'm from the South. We know guns.
血止住了
The bleeding stopped.
真正的痛苦要开始了
Now it's time for the real pain to begin.
我的继叔叔艾莫里召唤我见他
My step-uncle, Amory, has summoned me.
或是威廉和我过去 给他起的绰号:恶魔弟弟
Or as William and I used to call him: the demon brother.
来吧
Come on.
- 能明白为什么威廉远离家人 - 需要帮忙吗
- You can see why William stays away. - Do you need help?
- 不用 - 好的
- No. - Okay.
- 邀请函写了“白色” - 白色
- The invitation said "white." - White.
但他穿了米黄色 而那完全是灰色...
But then he's wearing beige, and that's fully gray--
莉莉 抱歉...莉莉
Oh, Lily, sorry. Sorry, Lily.
- 不 你没事 - 好的
- No, you're good. - Okay.
他在那里
There he is.
不好意思
Excuse me.
蕾根 我的生命之光
Regan, light of my life.
我终于见到我最爱的 光芒四射的继侄女了
Finally, I'm basking in the glow of my favorite step-niece.
艾莫里谷尔德 这位是墨瑟古德曼
Amory Gould, allow me to introduce Mercer Goodman.
古德曼先生 我不知道蕾根带了客人
Mr. Goodman. I wasn't aware Regan was bringing a guest.
你恢复得很快啊
You bounce back quick.
我们是在学校认识的
We know each other from school.
学生
A student?
老师 但我也是作家
Teacher, but I'm also a writer.
你写过我可能拜读过的作品吗
Have you written anything I might have read?
小说 纪实小说 《纽约客》的文章
A novel, roman à clef, perhaps a piece in the New Yorker?
我得承认我并非每一期 都会读到虚构小说那一栏
I must admit I don't get to the fiction in every issue,
但是我很喜欢里面的插画
but I do love the illustrations.
我没写过任何你可能读过的作品
I haven't written anything you might have read,
或任何人读过的作品
or anybody else for that matter.
但我打算很快做到这一点
But I'm planning to soon.
蕾根 他真惹人喜欢 他很乐观
Regan, he's delightful. He's so full of optimism.
我曾几何时也自称为作家
You know, I too once considered myself a bit of a writer.
可惜的是我的产出大部分是粪土
Unfortunately, what I churned out was mostly excrement
里面点缀了一些未能消化的珠玉 勉强可以算是妙语
studded with a few indigestible kernels of what once passed for wit.
但你知道 把我的笔记本烧毁
But you know, setting my notebooks aflame...
是我意识到自己是成年人的一刻
That was the moment when I realized I was an adult.
天啊 抱歉 失陪 认识你很高兴
Wow. Excuse me. It's very nice to meet you.
彼此彼此
Likewise.
没有谁比你更擅长打击人了
No one knows how to dismantle a person quite like you do.
蕾根 这话从你嘴里说出来 简直可以说是在夸赞了
Well, coming from you, Regan, that almost seems like a compliment.
并不是
It's not.
等等 我们得聊聊
Wait. We have to talk.
- 聊什么  - 你父亲
- About what? - About your father.
我知道 他通过了测试
I know. He passed his tests.
是 令人大松一口气
Yes, it was a great relief,
但在他面临官司的当口 这并不是什么好事
but it's not really much of a benefit when it's time for him to stand trial.
什么叫“官司”
What do you mean, "trial"?
我没办法委婉地说出来
There's no way to sugarcoat this.
明天 你父亲下飞机后将被逮捕
Tomorrow, when your father gets off the plane, he's going to be arrested.
因为什么被逮捕
Arrested for what?
金融罪 为了避税对若干资产估值过低
Financial crimes. Undervaluing certain assets for tax purposes.
为了取得贷款对资产估值过高
Overvaluing them to secure loans.
银行向联邦调查局举报了
The bank blew the whistle to the feds.
爸爸绝不会这么做的 一定是搞错了
Daddy would never. It's some kind of a mistake.
- 是别人犯的错 - 支票上是他的签名
- Someone else's wrongdoing. - His signature is on the checks.
房产文件上是他的姓 如果他们收回一栋 就能收回全部
It's his family name on the buildings. If they take one, they can take them all.
作为他的女儿和这间公司的首席营运官
Now, as his daughter and the COO of this company,
我们需要你给此事定下基调
we need you to set the tone.
好吗 我明天会安排一些 值得信任的顾问碰头
All right? I'm gonna gather a few trusted advisers tomorrow.
我们要定好一些关键说辞 我们需要统一战线
We're gonna set up some bullet points. We need a united front.
不
No!
回家吧
Just go home.
有人吗
Hello?
那边有人吗
Is there anybody in there?
有人吗
Hello?
天啊
Oh, my God.
帮帮忙...
Help! Help!
喂 是 我需要帮忙
Hello? Yes, I need help.
中央公园发生了枪击
There's been a shooting in Central Park.
我在第五大道和70多号街的路口 在东侧
I'm off of 5th and seventy-something, on the East Side.
拜托 请尽快赶来
Please, can you just come as soon as you can?
她要死了
She's dying.
帮帮忙 快来帮帮忙
Help! Anyone, please help!
小萨
Sam.
小萨 醒醒 小萨 拜托 小萨
Sam, wake up. Sam, come on, please. Sam!
她在那里
She's in there!
(纽约警察)
(消防局)
好
Yeah!
你在公园做什么
What were you doing in the park?
不知道 我不是...
I don't know. I wasn't--
我在等巴士 然后我听见某个声音
I was waiting for the bus, and I heard a noise.
我一开始以为是动物
I just thought it was an animal at first.
然后我走进公园
But then when I walked into the park,
对 那时我看到了她
Yeah, that's when I saw her.
- 你没在附近看到其他人  - 没有
- You didn't see anyone else in the area? - No.
- 当时很暗... - 帕尔撒警探
- It was just really dark-- - Detective Parsa?
麦克法登 曼哈顿北区 看来这是刚遇害
McFadden, Manhattan North. Looks like we caught a fresh one.
有什么发现
What do you got there?
这是女孩身上的
This was on the girl.
那是我的
That's mine.
那么 我猜这也是你的
Well then, I suppose this is yours too?
(改编自加斯瑞斯克哈尔伯格的小说)
字幕翻译:易晗